Kheel Center Current Documents Correspondence /4212
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Long Island Lighting Company, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  January 1977
- Loral Electronic Systems, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  April 1965
- Lorillard Company, P., 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Louisville and Nashville Railroad Co., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  April 12 1967
- McGill University, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  May 14 1976
- McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Macke Vending Company, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  October 28 1963
- MacFadden-Bartell Corporation, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Macy's, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  July 11 1964
- Management Information Center, Inc., 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- University of Manitoba (George S. Bain), 1963 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  June and July 1963
- Manufacturers Hanover Trust Company, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Manufacturing Chemists' Association, Inc., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  June 1964
- Marathon Oil Company, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  June 21 1965
- Marquette Cement Manufacturing Company, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  June 18 1964
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Massey-Ferguson, Inc., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  April 7 1965
- Maynard Research Council, Inc., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  March 7 1968
- Mead Corporation, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Mead Johnson and Company, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Mercy Hospital, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  August 7 1962
- Mesta Machine Company, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  January 13 1970
- Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, 1957-1968 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Metropolitan Lithographers Association, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  April 23 1965
- Metropolitan Transportation Authority, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  December 27 1968
- Metropolitan Washington Urban Coalition, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Michigan Bell Telephone Company, 1964-1983 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- University of Michigan, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Micro Methods Limited (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Milk Dealers' Association of Metropolitan New York, Inc., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  May 2 1966
- Minneapolis-Honeywell Regulator Co., 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- University of Minnesota, Labor Education Program, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  May 1964
- Mobil Oil Company, Inc., 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Monroe County Library System, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Montana Historical Society, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Montgomery Ward, 1966-1978 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- City of Montreal, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  November and December 1969
- Moore Business Forms, Inc., 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- More Chain Company, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  August 28 1964
- Mountain Bell, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  April 13 1982
- Mutual of New York, 1962-1968 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Mutual of Omaha, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  March 12 1965
- National Alliance of Businessmen, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  July and October 1968
- National Association for Public School Adult Education, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  September 15 1965
- National Association of Blue Shield Plans, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  March 31 1976
- National Association of Foremen, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  February 28 1956
- National Association of Furniture Manufacturers, Inc., 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- National Association of Manufacturers, 1955-1966 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- National Association of Suggestion Systems, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- National Bank of Detroit, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  January and February 1964
- National Broadcasting Company, 1962-1966 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 64)
- National Citizens' Committee for Community Relations, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  July 1968
- National Coal Association, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  August and December 1967
- National Coal Policy Conference, Inc., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  January 12 1966
- National Coat and Suit Industry Board, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- National Committee on Employment of Youth, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  October 9 1967
- National Conference of Police Associations, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  April 24 1968
- National Council for Industrial Peace, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  February 10 1969
- General Correspondence, National Council of the Churches of Christ, 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- National Council of Young Men's Christian Associations, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  March 9 1972
- National Economic Council, Inc., 1955-1965 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- National Education Association, 1966-1978 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- National Electrical Benefit Fund, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  June 22 1964
- National Electrical Contractors Association, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  August 13 1963
- National Electrical Contractors Association (New Jersey Chapter) (Box 2, Folder 78)
- National Electrical Manufacturers Association, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  May 1968
- National Electrical Manufacturers Association, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  August 15 1963
- National Farmers Union, 1963-1975 (Box 2, Folder 81)
- National Forest Products Association, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 82)
- National Foundation of Health, Welfare and Pension Plans, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 83)
- National Institute of Labor Education, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  February, March and April 1968
- National Institutes on Rehabilitation and Health Services, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 85)
- National Joint Board for Settlement Jurisdictional Disputes in Building and Construction Industry (Box 2, Folder 86)
  Paper
- National Lead Company, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  February and March 1966
- National Management Association, 1961-1965 (Box 2, Folder 88)
- National Office Management Association, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  April 8 1963
- National Planning Association, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  November 24 1964
- National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  March 10 1967
- National Railway Labor Conference, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 92)
- National Restaurant Association, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 93)
- National Retail Merchants Association, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 94)
- National Right to Work Committee, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  February 1967
- National Society of Professional Engineers, 1960-1965 (Box 2, Folder 96)
- National Tool and Die Manufacturers Association, 1962-1968 (Box 2, Folder 97)
- National Urban League, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  May and June 1969
- Nationwide Insurance, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  October and November 1962
- Howard Neitzert, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 100)
- Nelson Doubleday, Inc., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  September 17 1965
- New Bedford Cotton Manufacturing Association, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  September 14 1962
- New England Electric System, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 103)
- University of New Hampshire, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  November 25 1966
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 105)
- New York City Board of Education, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  November 3 1967
- New York City Department of Commerce and Industrial Development, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 107)
- New York City Commission on Human Rights, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  April and July 1968
- New York City Department of Personnel, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 109)
- New York City Labor Department, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  March 1968
- New York City Municipal Reference Library, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  April 25 1967
- The New York Public Library, 1962-1968 (Box 2, Folder 112)
- New York Shipping Association, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 113)
- N.Y.S. Commission for Human Rights, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  March 21 1967
- N.Y.S. Department of Audit and Control, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 115)
- New York State Department of Civil Service, 1963-1967 (Box 2, Folder 116)
- New York State Department of Commerce, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 117)
- New York State Department of Health, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 118)
- New York State Department of Labor, 1962-1967 (Box 2, Folder 119)
- New York State Department of Labor Division of Research and Statistics, 1962-1967 (Box 2, Folder 120)
- New York State Department of Law, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  April 29 1965
- New York State Department of Mental Hygiene, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  February, March and April 1964
- New York State Department of Social Services, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  April, July and November 1967
- New York State Division of Archives and History, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  November 1963
- New York State Division of Employment, 1963-1967 (Box 2, Folder 125)
- New York State Executive Department, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  April 23 1962
- New York State Job Development Authority, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  August 8 1966
- New York State Labor Relations Board, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  March and October 1967
- New York State Legislature, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 129)
- New York State Legislature, Committee on Industrial and Labor Conditions, 1963-1968 (Box 2, Folder 130)
- New York State Library, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  March and July 1966
- New York State-New Jersey Transportation Agency, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 132)
- New York State Public Employment Relations Board, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  September 1969
- New York State Women's Compensation Board, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  March 26 1964
- New York State University, 1967-1978 (Box 2, Folder 135)
- New York State University at Albany, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 136)
- New York State University at Stony Brook, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  November 10 1966
- New York Central Railroad (Box 2, Folder 138)
- New York Chamber of Commerce, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  April 27 1966
- New York Coat and Suit Association, Inc., 1962-1966 (Box 2, Folder 140)
- New York Railroad Association, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  January 1 1966
- New York Shipping Association, Inc., 1963-1967 (Box 2, Folder 142)
- New York State Building Industry Conference, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  September 23-25, 1962
- New York State Civil Service Employees Association, Inc., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  November 19 1965
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  May 3 1965
- New York State Personnel Council, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  December 23 1965
- New York Shipping Association, Inc., 1969 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  February 28 1969
- New York State Teachers Association, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  October and November 1965
- New York Stock Exchange, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  February 25 1964
- New York Telephone Company, 1963-1977 (Box 2, Folder 150)
- New York Times, 1967-1975 (Box 2, Folder 151)
- Newcomb and Sammons (Box 2, Folder 152)
  Address
- Newcomen Society in North America, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  February 11 1963
- Newspaper Personnel Relations Association, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  October 30 1962
- Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  October 11 1969
- Nichols Business Equipment, 1962-1966 (Box 2, Folder 156)
- North American Aviation, Inc., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  June and February 1962
- University of North Carolina, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  October 6 1964
- Northrop Carolina, Inc., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  November and December 1966
- Northwest Natural Gas Company, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  August 17 1962
- Northwestern Bell Telephone Company, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  February 3 1965
- Ohio Association of Retail Lumber Dealers, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  January and February 1962
- Ohio State Bar Association, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  July 7 1969
- Ohio State University, 1960-1964 (Box 2, Folder 164)
- Dorothy K. Oko, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 165)
- Oneida Ltd., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  March 13 1962
- Ontario Hydro, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 167)
- Oregon State University, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 168)
  December 12 1967
- Organization for Economic Co-Operation and Development, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 169)
- Oscar Mayer and Co., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 170)
  August 5 1964
- Otis Elevator Company, 1963-1967 (Box 2, Folder 171)
- Owens-Corning Fiberglass Corporation, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  August 1962
- Owen Illinois, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 173)
- Pacific Coast Association of Pulp and Paper Manufacturers, 1962-1969 (Box 2, Folder 174)
- Pacific Gas and Electric Company, 1964-1978 (Box 2, Folder 175)
- Pacific maritime Association, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 176)
- Pacific Mutual Life Insurance Company (Box 2, Folder 177)
- Pan American World Airways, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 178)
  September 18 1963
- Peavey Company, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 179)
- Penn-Central Merger Information Committee, 1962-1968 (Box 2, Folder 180)
- Pennsylvania Power and Light Company, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 181)
  December 9 1963
- Pennsylvania State University, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 182)
- Personnel Club of New York, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 183)
  November 18 1963
- Peru, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 184)
  January 26 1967
- Chas. Pfizer and Co., Inc., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 185)
  September 23 1965
- Pharmaceutical Manufacturers Association, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 186)
- City of Philadelphia, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 187)
  October 7 1968
- Philip Morris, Incorporated, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 188)
  July 31 1964
- Pitney-Bowes, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 189)
  November 15 1963
- City of Pittsburgh, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 190)
  November and December 1967
- Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Company, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 191)
  May 14 1964
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 192)
- University of Pittsburgh Graduate School of Social Work, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 193)
- Police Conference of New York, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 194)
  April 25 1968
- Port of New York Authority, 1962-1966 (Box 2, Folder 195)
- Princeton University, 1963-1970 (Box 2, Folder 196)
- Printing Industries of Metropolitan New York, Inc., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 197)
- Proctor and Gamble Company, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 198)
- Public Service Company of Colorado, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 199)
  November 5 1963
- Pullman-Standard, 1963-1967 (Box 2, Folder 200)
- Quaker Oats Company, 1969-1978 (Box 2, Folder 201)
- Queens College of the City University of New York, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 202)
  January 1969
- Queen's University Canada, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 203)
  September 23 1969
- Radio Corporation of America, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 204)
- Rand Corporation, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 205)
  November 9 1964
- Raytheon Company (Box 2, Folder 206)
- Remington Arms Company, Inc., 1964-1978 (Box 2, Folder 207)
- Republic Aviation Corporation, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 208)
  January 24 1963
- Republic Steel Corporation, 1963-1969 (Box 2, Folder 209)
- Reserve Mining Company (Box 2, Folder 210)
  Newspaper clipping
- Retirement Advisors, Inc., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 211)
- Revere Copper and Brass, Inc., 1961 (Box 2, Folder 212)
  May 9 1961
- R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 213)
  March 25 1968
- Rheen Manufacturing Co., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 214)
  November 23 1966
- Ritter Company, Inc., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 215)
  February 8 1965
- Rochester Public Library, 1959-1965 (Box 2, Folder 216)
- Rogers Corporation, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 217)
  June 11 1963
- Rohm and Haas Company (Box 2, Folder 218)
- Roth, William (Box 2, Folder 219)
- Rowntree, John A. (Fowler, Rowntree and Fowler), 1962-1966 (Box 2, Folder 220)
- Royal Bank of Canada, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 221)
  January 28 1965
- Rutgers University, 1962-1969 (Box 2, Folder 222)
- SAGE, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 223)
- St. Patrick's College (Box 2, Folder 224)
- St. Regis Paper Company, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 225)
  April 10 1964
- San Diego Gas and Electric Company, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 226)
  March 26 1968
- San Francisco Employers Council, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 227)
  November 27 1963
- San Francisco State College, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 228)
  March 8 1963
- Joseph Schlitz Brewing Company, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 229)
  April 28 1964
- Scott, Foresman and Company, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 230)
  August and October 1962
- Scott Paper Company, 1962-1968 (Box 2, Folder 231)
- Sears, Roebuck and Company, 1962-1978 (Box 2, Folder 232)
- Seyfarth, Shaw, Fairweather and Geraldson, 1960-1967 (Box 2, Folder 233)
- Shalita, Norman. Uganda Ministry of Labor (Box 2, Folder 234)
- Shatterproof Glass Corporation, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 235)
  October and November 1963
- Shell Oil Company, 1962-1978 (Box 2, Folder 236)
- Shwayder Brothers, Incorporated, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 237)
  April 14 1965
- Sidney Hillman Health Center, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 238)
  September 20 1967
- Sinclair Oil Corporation, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 239)
- Smith, Bob. Texas Instruments, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 240)
  August and September 1966
- Smith Kline and French Laboratories, 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 241)
- Smyth and Murphy Associates, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 242)
- Social Legislation Information Service, Inc., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 243)
  March 11 1966
- Sonoco Products Company, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 244)
- Sonneborn and Associates, Curt L., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 245)
  May 6 1963
- Sonoma State College, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 246)
  April and May 1964
- Southern Bell Telephone and Telegraph Co., 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 247)
- Southern New England Telephone Co., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 248)
  November 14 1963
- Southern Regional Education Board, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 249)
  May 24 1967
- Southern Tier Builders Association, Inc., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 250)
  August and September 1965
- Soviet Mission to the United Nations (Box 2, Folder 251)
- Special Libraries Association, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 252)
  March and November 1967
- Special Libraries Association Western New York Chapter, 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 253)
- Spinks, Geoffrey, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 254)
- Standard Bag Corporation, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 255)
  February 20 1962
- Standard Oil Company of California, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 256)
- Standard Oil Company (Indiana), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 257)
  May 11 1973
- Standard Oil Company (New Jersey), 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 258)
- Standard Oil Company, Ohio, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 259)
- Stanford Research Institute, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 260)
- Stanley Works, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 261)
- Stark, Arthur, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 262)
- State Farm Mutual Automobile Insurance Company, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 263)
  July 19 1978
- Steel, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 264)
- Sterling-Winthrop Research Institute, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 265)
  May and September 1964
- Stevenson, Jordan and Harrison, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 266)
- Students for a Democratic Society, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 267)
  April 11 1963
- Success Motivation Institute, Inc., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 268)
  February 4 1966
- Super Market Institute, Inc., 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 269)
- Swift and Co., 1967-1976 (Box 2, Folder 270)
- Sylvania Electric Products, Inc., 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 271)
- Syracuse University, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 272)
  June 16 1965
- Tab Products Company (Box 2, Folder 273)
- Tamiment Library (Box 2, Folder 274)
- Texaco, Inc., 1963-1977 (Box 2, Folder 275)
- University of Texas at Arlington, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 276)
  February and April 1970
- Thompson Ramo Woolridge Inc., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 277)
  February 6 1962
- The Timken Roller Bearing Company, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 278)
  May 4 1964
- University of Toronto, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 279)
- Training Within Industry Foundation, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 280)
- Transportation Association of America, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 281)
  July 29 1966
- Travelers' Insurance Co., 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 282)
- Truck Trailer Manufacturer Association, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 283)
  December 15 1964
- Union Bank, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Union Carbide Corporation, 1962-1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Union Electric Company, 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Uniroyal, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  September 19 1967
- United Hospital Fund of New York, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  April 1969
- U.S. Agency for International Development, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- U.S. Atomic Energy Commission, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- U.S. Bureau of Employment Security, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  May to December 1967
- U.S. Bureau of Employment Security States, 1960-1966 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- U.S. Bureau of Labor-Management Reports, 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- U.S. Bureau of Labor Standards, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1962-1967 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- U.S. Bureau of the Census, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  May 4 1966
- U.S. Civil Aeronautics Board, 1961-1965 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- U.S. Civil Service Commission, 1952-1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- U.S. Conference of Mayors, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  October 26 1967
- U.S. Congress, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- U.S. Department of Commerce, 1962-1966 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1964-1970 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- U.S. Department of Labor, 1965-1973 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- U.S. Department of Labor-Library, 1962-1969 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- U.S. Department of the Air Force, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  March 7 1966
- U.S. Department of the Interior, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- U.S. Department of the Navy, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- U.S. Federal Aviation Agency, 1964-1969 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- U.S. Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- U.S. General Accounting Office, 1963-1969 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- U.S. General Services Administration, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- U.S. Information Service, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  January 21 1964
- U.S. Library of Congress, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- U.S. National Archives, 1955-1966 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- U.S. National Labor Relations Board, 1963-1969 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- U.S. Office of Economic Opportunity, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- U.S. Office of Education, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  November 28 1966
- U.S. Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  January and March 1967
- U.S. Pacific Air Forces, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- U.S. Post Office Department, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  February 19 1964
- U.S. President's Council of Economic Advisors, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- U.S. President's Missile Sites Labor Commission, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- U.S. Railroad Retirement Board (Box 3, Folder 41)
- U.S. Railroad Retirement Board, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- U.S. Small Business Administration, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- U.S. Social Security Administration (Box 3, Folder 44)
- U.S> Subversive Activities Control Board, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- U.S. Unemployment Insurance Service, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- U.S. Veterans Administration, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- U.S. Women's Bureau, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- United States Conference of Mayors, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- United Fruit Company, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  April 3 1964
- United Prison Association of Massachusetts (Box 3, Folder 52)
- United States Gauge, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  March and April 1962
- M.P. Catherwood Library School Correspondence, 1959-1972 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- United States Industries, Inc., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  September 1 1964
- United States Steel Corp., 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- United Van Lines, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- University of Pennsylvania, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  May and June 1964
- University Research Center, Inc., 1967 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Upjohn Company, 1966-1978 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- W.E. Upjohn Institute, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Vermont University. Library, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- W.H.C.U., 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Walinsky, Adam, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Wall Street Journal, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- S.D. Warren Company Printers, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Washington, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  November 1963 - 1964
- Watertown Free Public Library, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  October, November and December 1969
- Weirton Steel Company, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  April 21 1965
- West Virginia Pulp and Paper, 1962-1969 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Western Electric Company, 1963-1969 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Westinghouse, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 73)